[{
  "question": "len(my_string)",
  "answer": "my_string.length();",
  "wrongAnswers": ["length(my_string)", "len(my_string.length())", "my_string.len()"]
},{
  "question": "my_string.lower()",
  "answer": "my_string.toLowerCase();",
  "wrongAnswers": ["tolower(my_string)", "my_string.toLower()", "my_string.lowerCase()"]
},{
  "question": "my_string.upper()",
  "answer": "my_string.toUpperCase();",
  "wrongAnswers": ["tolower(my_string)", "my_string.toUpper()", "my_string.upperCase()"]
},{
  "question": "my_string.strip()",
  "answer": "my_string.trim();",
  "wrongAnswers": ["trim(my_string)", "my_string.stripWhitespace()", "my_string.trimWhitespace()"]
},{
  "question": "my_string.replace('a', 'b')",
  "answer": "my_string.replace('a', 'b');",
  "wrongAnswers": ["my_string.substitute('a', 'b')", "replace(my_string, 'a', 'b')", "my_string.replace('b', 'a')"]
},{
  "question": "my_string.split(',')",
  "answer": "my_string.split(',');",
  "wrongAnswers": ["split(my_string, ',')", "my_string.explode(',')", "my_string.dividedBy(',')"]
},{
  "question": "'Hello' + my_string",
  "answer": "\"Hello\" + my_string;",
  "wrongAnswers": ["'Hello'.concat(my_string)", "concat('Hello', my_string)", "'Hello' + toString(my_string)"]
},{
  "question": "my_string.join(['a', 'b'])",
  "answer": "\"\".join(['a', 'b']);",
  "wrongAnswers": ["join(['a', 'b'], my_string)", "my_string.join(['a', 'b'])", "my_string.join('a', 'b')"]
},{
  "question": "my_string.startswith('Prefix')",
  "answer": "my_string.startsWith(\"Prefix\");",
  "wrongAnswers": ["startswith(my_string, 'Prefix')", "my_string.starts(\"Prefix\")", "my_string.beginsWith('Prefix')"]
},{
  "question": "my_string.endswith('Suffix')",
  "answer": "my_string.endsWith(\"Suffix\");",
  "wrongAnswers": ["endswith(my_string, 'Suffix')", "my_string.ends(\"Suffix\")", "my_string.finishesWith('Suffix')"]
}]